It's been an eventful journey for Polestar so far and not without obstacles,
这对Polestar来说是一次坎坷但不平凡的旅程
but through determination, innovation and an obsession with detail,
仰仗我们的决心、创新和对细节的执着
We finally arrived at a very exciting stage.
我们终于达到了一个激动人心的阶段：
VP, verification prototype build.
验证原型制造
It's one thing to design a car that challenges existing norms,
它是汽车设计中一项挑战常规的工作
while also raising the bar for electric cars the world over.
同时也将电动汽车提升至世界级水准
It's another thing entirely to realize that design in real life.
然而将这种设计变为现实又是另一回事。
From aesthetics to driver experience,
从美学到驾驶体验
no stone is left unturned during these builds.
我们不遗余力
The VP cars are the first build series and a major player in these prototype builds is carbon fiber.
原型车是首个生产系列，而构建它们的主角就是碳纤维
Carbon fiber figures hugely in the Polestar1.
碳纤维是Polestar1极其重要的组成部分
ten times stronger and five times lighter than steel.
比钢材强度高10倍，而重量却只有五分之一
Carbon fiber is the ideal material to realize the ambitious plans for this car
碳纤维是实现这个宏大计划的理想材料
to make the body more rigid and therefore create more responsive handling.
它使车身更坚固，因此带来了更敏捷的操控性
The entire upper body of the Polestar1 is carbon fiber reinforced polymer.
Polestar1整个车身上部是碳纤维增强聚合物(CFRP)
but that's not all.
这还不是全部
the true carbon fiber game changer is the dragonfly.
真正的碳纤维变革者是"蜻蜓"结构
A CFRP patch bonded to the steel underbody to increase torsional stiffness by 45%.
CFRP补片粘接到钢车身底板上，增加45%的抗扭刚度
The dragonfly, actually three parts,
"蜻蜓"结构实际上分为三部分
the body and the wings glued into place and fired in the oven at 85 degrees for 45 minutes also strengthens this traditionally weak point.
主体和翼片被粘接并放入烤箱，在85度下烘烤45分钟以加固原先的薄弱点
The next stop is the hang on parts area,
下一站是零件装夹处
where components are measured with unforgiving precision before they're attached.
总装前，零件将会在此以严苛的标准监测。
The slightest of misalignments can cause a disruption of the feature lines,
即使最轻微的错位也会造成特征线的中断
thus compromising the Polestar1's distinctive design.
从而破坏Polestar1的独特设计
Working with carbon fiber, however, can present different challenges.
处理碳纤维有很多难点
painting, for example,
以喷涂工艺为例
carbon fiber substrates aren't smooth and free of imperfections like steel,
碳纤维基材表面并不光滑，不像钢材那样完美
and they have a distinctive weave.
并且有独特的编织纹理
The solution,
解决办法是
a combination of machine sanding and hand sanding to give the panels a smooth, even finish
一系列的机器和手工打磨加工出组件的光滑表面
fine sanding is done by hand to ensure the integrity of the feature lines and to stay true to the initial design.
精磨由手工完成，确保特征线与初始设计一致
The marriage point is the true test of all this exacting measurement.
组装点是对之前严格测量结果的一次真正测试
Where the chassis is attached to the body.
这个阶段，底盘将和车身合装(marriage)
The parts are attached by a series of bolts protruding from the chassis,
它们之间由一系列底盘突出的螺栓固定
which then slide into the upper body.
这些螺栓之后会插入车身
If even one of the bolts is misaligned
即使有一个螺栓没有校准
the process must begin again.
整个过程都要推倒重来
With every Union performed, the process goes more smoothly.
得益于每个团体的出色工作，生产进程也更加顺利
This means fewer adjustments and a shorter construction time
这意味着更少的调整耗时和更短的生产时间
closer and closer to perfection with each marriage.
也使得每次合装都更加臻于完美
双语字幕：@PolestarX